let questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: ["Yes", "No", "Machine dependent", "None of the mentioned"]
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "Select the correct option to draw a rectangle centred at 50,50 with width and height as 50, 70 respectively.",
    answer: "Canvas.create_rectangle(50,50,50,70)",
    options: [
      "Canvas.create_rect(50,50,50,70)",
      "Canvas.create_rect(50,70,50,50)",
      "Canvas.create_rectangle(50,50,50,70)",
      "Tkinter.create_rect(50,50,50,70)"
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "What will be the value of the following Python expression?" +
      "<br>" +
      "<br>" +
      "4 + 3 % 5",
    answer: "7",
    options: ["4", "7", "2", "0"]
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      " What will be the output of the following Python code?" +
      "<br>" +
      "<br>" +
      "x = ['ab', 'cd']" +
      "<br>" +
      "for i in x:" +
      "<br>" +
      "</t>" +
      "i.upper()" +
      "<br>" +
      "print(x)",
    answer: "[‘ab’, ‘cd’]",
    options: [
      "[‘ab’, ‘cd’]",
      "[‘AB’, ‘CD’]",
      " [None, None]",
      "none of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: " What happens when '2' == 2 is executed?",
    answer: "False",
    options: ["True", "False", " ValueError occurs", "Type Error occurs"]
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      " What is the output of the following?" +
      "<br>" +
      "<br>" +
      "print([i.lower() for i in 'HELLO'])",
    answer: "['h','e','l','l','o']",
    options: ["'hello'", "['hello']", " ['h','e','l','l','o']", "hello"]
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Select the correct code to create a check button under parent frame1 and it should be bind to v1?",
    answer:
      "Checkbutton(frame1 , text=''Bold’’ ,variable=v1 ,command=processCheckbutton)",
    options: [
      "CheckButton(frame1, text=''Bold'' , command=CheckButton)",
      "Checkbutton(frame.set(f1) ,text.set(''bold'') ,command=v1.set(processCheckbutton)",
      " Checkbutton(frame1,text=''Bold'',variable=v1.set(),command=v1.set(processCheckbut ton)",
      "Checkbutton(frame1 , text=''Bold’’ ,variable=v1 ,command=processCheckbutton)"
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      " What Python built-in function returns the unique number assigned to an object",
    answer: "id()",
    options: ["identity()", "refnum()", " ref()", "id()"]
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "Which code can be used as an input dialog named ''Is this a character? ''",
    answer:
      "Tkinter.messagebox.askyesno(''askyesno'' , ''Is this a character? '')",
    options: [
      "Tkinter.messagebox.showerror(''showerror'' , ''Is this a character? '')",
      "Tkinter.messagebox.askyesno(''askyesno'' , ''Is this a character? '')",
      "Tkinter.messagebox.showinfo(''showinfo'' , ''Is this a character? '')",
      "Tkinter.messagebox.showwarning(''showwarning'' , ' 'Is this a character? '')"
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      " Choose the correct function from the following list to get the random integer between 99 to 200, which is divisible by 3.",
    answer: "random.randrange(99, 200, 3)",
    options: [
      "random.randrange(99, 200, 3)",
      "random.randint(99, 200, 3)",
      "random.random(99, 200, 3)",
      "random.randdint(99, 201, 3)"
    ]
  }
];
